
var newTrivia = [
	{
		"question" : "What sport is Shannon in?",
		"answer" : "Cross Country",
	},
	{
		"question" : "What is Kelsey and Alyssa's favorite soccer team?",
		"answer" : "Orlando City Soccer",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Whose birthday is on a Spanish holiday?",
		"answer" : "Jim, May 5th",
	},
	{
		"question" : "What book does Katie collect?",
		"answer" : "Little Women",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Who is currently employed by another family member at Alstom?",
		"answer" : "Nicole",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Who retired in 2016?",
		"answer" : "John",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Who is the only family member who has had pink hair?",
		"answer" : "Chris",
	},
	{
		"question" : "What school does Sarah currently attend?",
		"answer" : "Parsons the New School of Design",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Who is obbessed with Dr.Pepper Cherry?",
		"answer" : "Tom",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Who wears shorts all winter?",
		"answer" : "LJ",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Who is most scared of their boss?",
		"answer" : "Nicole",
	},
	{
		"question" : "What is the model of car Jessica recently purchased?",
		"answer" : "Jeep Renegade",
	},
	{
		"question" : "How many colors has Mart dyed her hair?",
		"answer" : "5 (Purple, Brown, Green, Platnium Blonde and Blue.)",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Who graduates high school in 2018?",
		"answer" : "Andrew",
	},
	{
		"question" : "What music festival has Josh attended five times?",
		"answer" : "Bonnaroo Music Festival",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Who was in South Carolina in January 2017?",
		"answer" : "Kelsey and Alyssa",
	},
	{
		"question" : "What is Alyssa's current professional field?",
		"answer" : "Interior Design",
	},
	{
		"question" : "What song do we sing in celebration of another family member?",
		"answer" : "Here's to you...",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Where was James Joseph Hennessy (Pop-Pop's grandfather) born?",
		"answer" : "Cork, Ireland",
	},
	{
		"question" : "What was Grandpa's fathers name?",
		"answer" : "James Harrigan Hennessy",
	},
	{
		"question" : "What is Tom's middle name?",
		"answer" : "Joseph",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Fill in the blank: The 2017 Hennessy Reunion is the ___ Annual.",
		"answer" : "61st",
	},
	{
		"question" : "What year did Kelsey and Alyssa get married?",
		"answer" : "In 2014",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Who joined the doctor club this year?",
		"answer" : "Jessica",
	},
	{
		"question" : "What is Kendra's maiden name?",
		"answer" : "Roberts",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Who tweeted about Hockey 226 times in the month of March alone?",
		"answer" : "Mart",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Who cut off 15in of their own hair in 2017?",
		"answer" : "Sarah",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Who did Johnny proclaim the 2016 Amity Lake Bass Champion! ?",
		"answer" : "Joe",
	},
	{
		"question" : "How many family members have worked at Short's Deli?",
		"answer" : "5- Nicole, Jess, Mart, Katie, Sarah",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Where was James Harigan Hennessy born?",
		"answer" : "Buffalo, New York",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Where did Pop-pop say the secret was in his mac and cheese?",
		"answer" : "The sauce",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Name the cousins in correct order from oldest to youngest.",
		"answer" : "Johnny, Greg, Peter, Nicole, Jessica, Josh, Kelsey, Mart, Katie, Sarah, Sammy, Andrew, Shea, Shannon ",
	},
	{
		"question" : "How many family members have attended St. Bonaventure?",
		"answer" : "4- Pop-pop, Nicole, Jessica, Mart",
	},
	{
		"question" : "How many TV's are in the Amity Lake house?",
		"answer" : "7",
	},
	{
		"question" : "How many beds are in the Amity Lake house?",
		"answer" : "7",
	},
	{
		"question" : "Name the states our family currently lives in?",
		"answer" : "New York, Maryland, Florida, Connetticut, California",
	},
	{
		"question" : "What year was the addition added to the house?",
		"answer" : "2001",
	},
	{
		"question" : "How many people were born ten years apart?",
		"answer" : "6 sets(Nicole-Johnny, Jessie-Shea, Tom-Kendra, Nicole-Andrew, Peter-Twins, John-Margaret)",
	},
	{
		"question" : "How many people have been a flower girl for someone else?",
		"answer" : "3 - Nicole, Jessica, Shannon",
	},
	{

		"question" : "What town was Pop-pop born in?",
		"answer" : "Buffalo, New York",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Name the order of the Original 8 from oldest to youngest.",
		"answer" : "Aunt Betty, Uncle Jimmy, Uncle Bill, Pop-pop, Aunt Mary Ellen, Aunt Cackle, Uncle Tom, Aunt Agnes",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who will be graduating school in 2019?",
		"answer" : "Sarah and Shea",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most likely to be taking a nap'?",
		"answer" : "Nicole",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most likely to take pictures'?",
		"answer" : "Mary",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most likely to get out of cleaning dishes'?",
		"answer" : "Jessica",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most Competitive'?",
		"answer" : "Jim",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most likely to rock the irish jig'?",
		"answer" : "Andrew",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Best Hugger'?",
		"answer" : "Greg",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most likely to be at Disney'?",
		"answer" : "Kelsey and Alyssa",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most likely to be politicaly correct'?",
		"answer" : "The twins, Mart and Katie",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most likely to drink all of the Sunny D'?",
		"answer" : "Sammy",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most likely to spill a secret'?",
		"answer" : "Josh",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most likely to insult someone with a smile on his face'?",
		"answer" : "Johnny",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most likely to play with your hair'?",
		"answer" : "Shea",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most likely to buy a new pair of shoes'?",
		"answer" : "Kelsey",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most likely to talk about Disney'?",
		"answer" : "The whole family",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most likely to throw up the peace sign'?",
		"answer" : "Joe",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Best All Around'?",
		"answer" : "Grandpa",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most likely to fall off the scooter'?",
		"answer" : "Mart",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most likely to Call and Sing Happy Birthday'?",
		"answer" : "The Sanfords",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most likely to live in the shed'?",
		"answer" : "Michael the bad guy",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who was written in as 'Most likely to bring their harmonic to a family gathering'?",
		"answer" : "Andrew",
	},
	{
		
		"question" : "Who didn't understand the meaning of a 'write in' and just wrote 'grandma is awesome', ' grandma playing the banjo' and 'grandma'?",
		"answer" : "Sammy",
	},

]